https://www.intevac.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home » Privacy Policy
Who We Are
Please visit our Company profile page to learn more about Intevac.
What Personal Data We Collect and Why We Collect It
Online Forms
This site collects generic, anonymous statistical data that gives us information about which pages people visit, how they came to this site, and their general location.
Contact Forms: This form collects the necessary data needed to answer your questions or address your comments.Online Employment Application Form: This form collects the necessary data to allow us to evaluate your suitability for a specific job position.
Embedded Content From Other Websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
This site collects generic, anonymous statistical data that gives us the information what pages people visit, how they came to this site, and their general location. This data does not contain any personal information that be used to identify specific site visitors.
Who We Share Your Data With
We do not share your data with any third parties.
How Long We Retain Your Data
Data submitted through online forms is retained for 30 days. In the case of employment applications, we may keep your uploaded resumes on file indefinitely.
What rights you have over your data
If you have submitted personal information through online forms on this site, you can request to receive an exported file of that personal data. You can also request deletion any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Company
OverviewSupportCareersSupplier/Customer T’s & C’sInvestors
News & Events
Press ReleasesEvents & Presentations
Thin Film Equipment
OverviewHard Disk Drive (HDD)Display Cover PanelSolarAdvanced Packaging
Photonics
OverviewMilitaryCommercial
Contact
Thin Film EquipmentPhotonicsInvestor RelationsGeneral Inquiries
Company
Overview
Support
Careers
Supplier/Customer T’s & C’s
Investors
News & Events
Press Releases
Events & Presentations
Thin Film Equipment
Overview
Hard Disk Drive (HDD)
Display Cover Panel
Solar
Advanced Packaging
Photonics
Overview
Military
Commercial
Contact
Thin Film Equipment
Photonics
Investor Relations
General Inquiries
© 2020 Intevac, Inc. | All Rights Reserved | Privacy | Conflict Minerals Policy
Username or Email Address
Password
Remember Me
Search for:
Search for:
CompanyMissionManagementLocationsSupplier/Customer T’s & C’sThin Film EquipmentOverviewHard Disk Drive (HDD)Display Cover PanelSolarAdvanced PackagingPhotonicsOverviewMilitaryCommercialSupportCareersPositionsCulture/BenefitsInternshipsInvestorsNews & EventsPress ReleasesEvents & PresentationsContactThin Film EquipmentPhotonicsInvestor RelationsGeneral Inquiries
